<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo SEO theme</title>
    <link>http://thirdhemisphere.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hugo SEO theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://thirdhemisphere.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Friday the 13th Unlucky? Triskaidekaphobia or the Fear of thirteen</title>
      <link>http://thirdhemisphere.net/meaning-of-kinships/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thirdhemisphere.net/meaning-of-kinships/</guid>
      <description>Friday the thirteenth is feared by some but ignored by most. The thirteenth day of the month falling on a Friday is not a good time to walk under a ladder because you might trip over a black cat and shatter a mirror into a thousand pieces. Fear of the number thirteen, or triskaidekaphobia, is the irrational fear that this number negatively influences our fortunes. Why is Friday the 13th Unlucky?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aboriginal Art Symbols in Dot Painting: Larapinta Dreaming</title>
      <link>http://thirdhemisphere.net/articles/aboriginal-art-symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thirdhemisphere.net/articles/aboriginal-art-symbols/</guid>
      <description>The ancestors of today&amp;#39;s Aboriginal people populated the Australian continent about tens of thousands of years ago. Their culture is in many respects unique because, until the eighteenth century, they had limited contact with people outside Australia. One of the most striking manifestations of contemporary Aboriginal culture are the iconic dot paintings of the desert people. Dot paintings include many Aboriginal art symbols that convey meaning to the work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>